{
    "id": "bbe3504030464a778577192a854d6c0e",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will call you ………………………… I hear from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "as far as",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bafea1e84af441db86b652012f55d2a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… it was a tough task, I managed to finish it.",
            "description": "Though is a conjunction used to connect two contrasting ideas. Despite is a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "659da68093724231989639294f62a9e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Intelligent ………………………. she was, she couldn’t pass the test.",
            "description": "Intelligent as she was or intelligent though she was means the same as though she was intelligent.",
            "answers": [
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1829900f932340c39e9fae460eb8bb25"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know the reason ……………………….. she hates me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "why",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33a2e0d828b34b7db53c4c0d93a91600"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ………………………… calculator had been stolen complained to the teacher.",
            "description": "The girl complained to the teacher. Her calculator had been stolen. The relative pronoun whose replaces possessive pronouns like her, his, their etc.",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d94a10c3bd2f4afe9a7d1242880369f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last month I watched an interesting movie the name of ……………………….. I don’t remember.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06e7c9fac4764ac4965930f127ad95b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We bought some mangoes from ……………………………. we extracted juice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52abfc981b804743a0ccb2ac437030f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She married a handsome architect ………………………….. she met on social media.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses, that can replace whom in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c546b9469b8f4e5aad7f9fed201ae776"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to a store …………………………. they sell Indian spices.",
            "description": "There can mean in which or at which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f290fbda24d5457c927e7d6aa39d7e50"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you had been careful, you wouldn’t have made this mistake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10447d51bf4c46ea9feda65cb6daf6c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… we act now, we will lose this opportunity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "503c8dc47caf4461865e976e8146fbf2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no idea ……………………………… she is talking about.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45d8b4eee9044d748dced2f4b9874cdf"
        }
    ]
}